clickdensity.com 2011-11-24

# Clickdensity - Evaluate & Improve your Website: Heat Maps & More

Version 2 - 13th September 2011

clickdensity.com is wholly owned and operated by Box UK Limited.

Box UK respects the privacy needs of our customers. This Privacy Policy outlines what specific information is gathered on the Clickdensity website and how that information is used.

If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please feel free contact us at info@clickdensity.com.

**1\. Who we are**

In this Privacy Policy references to "we", "us" and "our" are to Box UK Limited.

**2\. What information we collect and how**

The information we collect via Clickdensity may include:

a. Any personal details you type in and submit, such as name, address, email address, etc.

b. Your IP address (this is your computer's individual identification number) which is automatically logged by our web server.

c. Your preferences and use of email updates, recorded by emails we send you (if you select to receive email updates on products and offers).

d. Session information stored in cookies, these do not include any personal information and are used to ensure the correct data is extracted from the database when using our interactive systems. 

e. Under no circumstances will we hold sensitive payment details such as your card number, expiry date and security code. All transactions are handled through our accredited payment bureau, Worldpay Ltd. For more information on Worldpay's privacy policy please refer to http://www.worldpay.co.uk. 

**3\. What we do with your information**

Any personal information we collect from this website will be used in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and other applicable laws. The details we collect will be used:-

a. To process your order, to provide after-sales service (we may pass your details to another organisation to supply/deliver products or services you have purchased and/or to provide after-sales service). 

b. To comply with legal requirements.

c. In certain cases we may use your email address to send you information on our other products and services. In such a case you will be offered the option to opt in/out before completing your purchase. 

**4\. Information security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorised access to or unauthorised alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorised access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to Box UK employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

**5\. Data integrity**

Box UK processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

**6\. Policy Modifications**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when Box UK makes changes to this Privacy Policy, we will highlight the changes on our homepage and email users who have given us permission to do so. If the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.

**7\. Contacting Box UK about Privacy**

If you have any questions about our privacy statement, the information we have collected from you online, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact:

Box UK  
Westgate Court  
Westgate Street  
Cardiff  
CF10 1DD  
United Kingdom 

Box UK is registered with the Data Protection Register (Registration Number: Z9488852).
